module.exports = {
	config: {
		name: "Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ", // Name of command, it must be unique to identify with other commands
		version: "1.0", // Version of command
		author: "Eslam", // Author of command
		countDown: 5, // Time to wait before executing command again (seconds)
		role: 0, // Role of user to use this command (0: normal user, 1: admin box chat, 2: owner bot)
		shortDescription: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  mÃ´ táº£ ngáº¯n cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "this is short description of command"
		}, // Short description of command
		longDescription: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  mÃ´ táº£ dÃ i cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "this is long description of command"
		}, // Long description of command
		category: "categoryName", // Category of command
		guide: {
			vi: "Ä‘Ã¢y lÃ  hÆ°á»›ng dáº«n sá»­ dá»¥ng cá»§a lá»‡nh",
			en: "this is guide of command"
		} // Guide of command
	},

	langs: {
		vi: {
			hello: "xin chÃ o",
			helloWithName: "xin chÃ o, id facebook cá»§a báº¡n lÃ  %1"
		}, // Vietnamese language
		en: {
			hello: "hello world",
			helloWithName: "hello, your facebook id is %1"
		} // English language
	},

	// onStart is a function that will be executed when the command is executed
	onStart: async function ({ api, args, message, event, threadsData, usersData, dashBoardData, globalData, threadModel, userModel, dashBoardModel, globalModel, role, commandName, getLang }) {
		// YOUR CODE HERE
    
              let questions = [
                {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²:ÙˆØ¬Ù‡ Ù…Ø¨ØªØ³Ù…  ",
                  answer: "ðŸ˜ƒ"
                },
                {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø±Ø¬Ù„ Ø²Ùˆ Ø´Ø¹Ø± Ø§Ø¨ÙŠØ¶",
                  answer: "ðŸ‘¨â€ðŸ¦³"
                },
                {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø±Ø¬Ù„ ÙŠØ±ÙØ¹ ÙŠØ¯Ùˆ",
                  answer: "ðŸ™‹â€â™‚ï¸"
                },
                {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²:  Ù„Ø³Ø§Ù† ",
                  answer: "ðŸ‘…"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ù‚Ø¨Ø¹Ø©",
                  answer: "ðŸ§¢"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø±Ø¬Ù„ Ø²ÙˆÙ…Ø¨ÙŠ ",
                  answer: "ðŸ§Ÿâ€â™‚ï¸"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: ÙˆØ¬Ù‡ ØºØ§Ø¶Ø¨",
                  answer: "ðŸ˜¡"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: ÙˆØ¬Ù‡ ÙŠØ¶Ø­ Ø¨Ø¯Ù…ÙˆØ¹",
                  answer: "ðŸ˜‚"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: ÙˆØ¬Ù‡ Ø­Ø²ÙŠÙ†",
                  answer: "ðŸ˜”"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø±Ø¬Ù„ Ù…Ø¨Ø±Ù…Ø¬",
                  answer: "ðŸ‘¨â€ðŸ’»"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø±Ø¬Ù„ Ø·Ø¨Ø§Ø®",
                  answer: "ðŸ‘¨â€ðŸ³"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø´Ø±Ø·ÙŠ",
                  answer: "ðŸ‘¨â€âœˆï¸"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ ÙÙŠ Ø¹ÙŠÙ†ÙŠÙ‡ Ø§Ù„Ø­Ø¨",
                  answer: "ðŸ˜"
                }, {
                  question: "Ù…Ù† ÙŠØ±Ø³Ù„ Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ Ù‡Ø§Ø°Ø§ Ø§Ù„ÙˆØµÙ Ø§ÙˆÙ„Ø§ ÙŠÙÙˆØ²: ÙŠÙ„Ù‚ÙŠ ØªØ­ÙŠØ© Ø§Ù„Ø´Ø±Ø·ÙŠ",
                  answer: "ðŸ«¡"
                },
              ];
              let randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * questions.length);
              let randomQuestion = questions[randomIndex].question;
              let answer = questions[randomIndex].answer;
              api.sendMessage(randomQuestion, event.threadID, (err, messageInfo)=>{
                let stopListening = api.listenMqtt((err, event) => {
                if (err) return console.error(err);
api.setOptions({listenEvents: true});
                switch (event.type) {
                  case "message":
                    if(event.threadID === messageInfo.threadID){
                      if (event.body === answer) {               api.sendMessage("Ø¬Ù…ÙŠÙ„ Ø§Ù†Øª Ø³Ø±ÙŠØ¹", event.threadID, event.messageID);
                      return listenEmitter.stopListening();
                    } else if (event.body === 'Ø§ÙŠÙ…ÙˆØ¬ÙŠ') {
                      return listenEmitter.stopListening();
                    }
                    api.markAsRead(event.threadID, (err) => {
                      if (err) console.log(err);
                    });
                    }

                    break;
                }
              });
              });

	}
};